Hello, this is Ria
In today's podcast, we're going to speak Korean slowly.
It's already 2026. It's a new year, 'Saehae'.
Happy New Year
. Let's make goals for 2026 together today.
My first plan is to study languages.
I'm studying Chinese and Japanese right now,
but I'm busy... I can't do it often.
I'm just studying little by little.
How do you guys study Korean?
Please tell me.
I try hard to study vocabulary.
I'll tell you my goals.
I want to go to China and Japan this year, 2026.
I want to have conversations in Chinese and Japanese there.
It seems fun.
You guys are learning Korean.
What do you want to do first in Korean?
My second goal is to exercise.
Exercise is really important,
but I always put it off.
Why do I put it off?
I find it too bothersome to exercise.
From now on, I'm going to change my habits.
I'm going to exercise about three times a week.
Do you guys exercise a lot?
Where do you exercise?
It's winter in Korea, so it's really cold. It's cold.
I don't like cold weather.
I wish spring would come soon.
These days, I usually exercise at home.
It's called home training.
Everyone just calls it home training
. I usually do home training in the winter.
Many people use numbers when they make plans.
For example, "I'm going to lose 5 kg,"
"I 'm going to go on a diet,"
"I absolutely have to lose 10 kg," "
I have to get 100 points on my test."
But I don't want to do that.
I want to focus on today rather than numbers.
Make a plan for each day and stick to it
. Then I feel proud of myself. I'm satisfied with myself.
That's it
It's okay if you can't stick to today's plan.
You can do better tomorrow.
Don't stress about numbers, everyone!
Just focus on this moment every day.
I want to be healthier this year
and cook a lot of healthy food.
I really like cooking.
There's a program that's popular in Korea these days.
Have you heard of ?
The food there looks so delicious.
The food I wanted to eat the most there was galbi.
Galbi is really delicious.
My third goal is to read a lot of books.
In 2025, to be honest, I didn't read many books last year.
I make a lot of videos,
so sometimes my eyes really hurt and
my eyes are tired.
So I want to read a book instead of using my phone.
Reading a paper book makes me feel at ease and
helps me concentrate better.
But these days, people don't read books much.
So I want to read more diligently.
But why didn't I read a lot last year?
I was really busy.
But actually, that's an excuse.
Even if you really don't have time, you can read a book sometimes.
If you do it little by little every day, it becomes a habit.
I think doing it every day is important,
just like we do Duolingo every day.
I'll tell you about my daily routine later.
My fourth goal is to travel a lot.
Last year, I traveled to many countries,
especially Asian countries.
So! This year, I want to go further.
Where should I go?
Please recommend
If there’s a place in your country I should visit, please recommend it to me.
I'll visit later.
I like traveling.
I can see beautiful scenery when I travel.
It's different from Korea, so it's interesting.
I especially like going to the supermarket when I travel
. Suddenly, a supermarket?
If you go to the supermarket, you can easily learn about the food culture of that country.
In Korea, there aren't many kinds of cheese and they're expensive.
On the other hand, in European countries, there are many kinds of cheese.
When you go abroad, there are fruits that aren't in Korea
. Have you ever tried 'Sukga'?
I've never eaten this fruit in Korea.
Many Koreans... I don't know this fruit well.
I tried it for the first time last year.
I had high expectations, but it was just okay.
'Just okay' means neither good nor bad.
A similar word is just so-so.
For example, if I ask you guys,
what do you think of the new Korean drama that came out on Netflix?
Then you can say, "Just okay" or "Just okay."
I usually say it with this expression.
Now look at my expression.
Just okay.
Do you know what I mean?
My last goal
is to make a lot of good videos this year.
I want you to become good at Korean after watching my videos.
So I'm going to work hard on making videos.
Learning Korean is really hard
, but I want to make it easy.
That's my role .
Are you ready to study hard with me?
I've talked about my goals so far.
Now it's your turn.
Write down your New Year's resolutions for 2026 in the comments.
Then, let's check those goals together next year.
That's all for today's video.
I'll be posting photos of my daily life on my Instagram from now on.
Please check out my membership too
There you can find study materials and quizzes
See you next time!
Happy New Year!
Thank you :)